{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "hello",
      "answer": "hi welcome"
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "answer": "you didnt enter any thing"
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "answer": "you didnt enter any thing"
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "& \"C:/Program Files/Python313/python.exe\" p:/coding/pyoop/py/ai.py",
      "answer": "exit"
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "answer": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "",
      "answer": "none"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is the capital of france",
      "answer": "paris"
    },
    {
      "question": "how can i make the bread of flour",
      "answer": "you can search on that"
    },
    {
      "question": "how can i download minecarft",
      "answer": "you can search on that"
    },
    {
      "question": "how can i make a ai",
      "answer": "you can search on that"
    },
    {
      "question": "how can i learn java\\",
      "answer": "you can search on that"
    }
  ]
}